Guide to the Bella Abzug papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: Legislative Files
  - Subseries VI.2: Legislation Sponsored by Abzug
    - 93rd Congress--1974 (Box 694)
      - Economy HR 14285 HR 15737 (Box 694)
      - Education HR 12618 HR 13648 HR 14703 (Box 694)
      - Education, Labor H.J.Res. 999 (Box 694)
      - Education & Sports HR 13756 (Box 694)
      - Employment HR 13829 HR 16150 HR 15970 HR 1415-empty (Box 694)
      - Energy HR 12488 HR 12888 HR 14647 (Box 694)
      - Energy Crisis H.Res.1024 (Box 694)
      - Energy--Oil COB. HR 13783 (Box 694)
      - Environment HR 13951 (Box 694)
      - Export Administration. HR 14860 HR 15768 (Box 694)
      - Federal Procurement HR 15233 (Box 694)
      - Foreign Affairs H.Con.Res.41 H.J.Res.930 HR 14153 HR 14626 (Box 694)
      - For.Affs.-Olympics H.Con.Res. 41 (Box 694)
      - For. & Interstate Affairs HR 12582 (Box 694)
      - Foreign Investment. HR 241 (Box 694)
      - Foreign Policy H.J.Res.268 H.J.Res 522 (Box 694)
      - Government Operations H.Res.865 H.Res.1015 (Box 695)
      - Grand Jury HR 13912 (Box 695)
      - Greece HR 14153 (Box 695)
      - Health HR 13651 HR 13971 HR 14121 HR 13995 HR 14486 (Box 695)
      - House Administration HR 13903 (Box 695)
      - Housing HR 16202 HR 14779 (Box 695)
      - Immigration HR 16402 HR 13927 (Box 695)
      - Impeachment HR 13094 H.Con.Res. 54 H.Con.Res. 54 H.Con.Res.54 (Box 695)
      - Income Averaging HR 12423 (Box 695)
      - Information HR 16156 (Box 695)
      - Income Tax HR 16293 (Box 695)
      - Internal Revenue HR 16196 (Box 695)
      - IRS/Oil Companies HR 12595 (Box 695)
      - IRS Code HR 15452 (Box 695)
      - Interstate Commerce HR 10227 (Box 695)
      - Investments HR 15488 (Box 695)
      - Israel H.Res.1118 (Box 695)
      - Jewry, Soviet HR 1190; HR 6386; H.Res.567 H.Con.Res.49( H.Con.Res.391) (Box 695)
      - Judiciary HR 14223 (Box 695)
      - King, Martin L. H.Con.Res.46 (Box 695)
      - Lotteries HR 15922 (Box 695)
      - Mail Privilege HR 15998 (Box 695)
      - Man. H.J.Res.l099 (Box 695)
      - Migrant Workers HR 12557 (Box 695)
      - National Historic Sites HR 13157 (Box 695)
      - National Homestead Act HR 12566 (Box 695)
      - News Media HR 15242 (Box 695)
      - Nixon HR 1367 (Box 695)
      - Nuclear Agreement H.Res.1219 (Box 695)
      - Nuclear Technology H.J.Res.l092 (Box 695)
      - Parks / Animals HR 13004 (Box 695)
      - Petroleum HR 15462 (Box 695)
      - Political Management/Campaigns HR 16235 (Box 695)
      - Post Office H.J.Res.924 (Box 695)
      - President HR 14818 H.J.Res.993 (Box 695)
      - Prison Inmates HR 16160 (Box 695)
      - Privacy HR 15524 HR 14435 (Box 695)
      - Procurement HR 15233 (Box 695)
      - Protein Production HR 15892 (Box 695)
      - Public Funds HR 15072 (Box 695)
      - Public Opinion HR 16012 (Box 695)
      - Public Utilities HR 16018 (Box 695)
      - Public Works HR 14884 HR 14569 HR 14011 HR 13627 HR 13157 HR 9483; HR 10107 (Box 695)
      - Rape Prevention HR 14366 (Box 695)
      - Roosevelt, E. H.J.Res.l022 (Box 695)
      - Senior Citizens HR 4636--emp H.Res.1264 H.Res.1191 (Box 695)
      - Sewall-Belmont House HR 15975 (Box 695)
      - Sex Discrimination HR 14752 (Box 695)
      - Social Security HR 14809 HR 14139 HR 12630 (Box 695)
      - SSI HR 15157 HR 12770-1277 HR 12903 HR 14418 (Box 695)
      - Transportation HR 12356 HR 10853 (Box 695)
      - Veterans HR 13184 HR 13977 (Box 695)
      - Welfare HR 13916 (Box 695)
      - Wilderness HR 15879 (Box 695)
    - 93rd Congress: (Box 696)
      - House Resolutions (Box 696)
      - House Concurrent Resolutions (Box 696)
      - House Joint Resolutions (Box 696)
      - Bills No.1-10,000 (Box 696)
      - Bills No. 10,001-20,000 (Box 696)
    - 94th Congress: (Box 697)
      - Legislation--General (Box 697)
      - Adoption, HR 4901 (Box 697)
      - Age Requirements H.J.Res.175 (Box 697)
      - Agriculture HR 8881; HR 8347; HR 8165; HR 10776 (Box 697)
      - Aid/Assistance HR 8469; HR 12878 (Box 697)
      - Airlines HR 2149 (Box 697)
      - Amnesty HR 1229; HR 2568 (Box 697)
      - Animals HR 6583; HR 9217 (Box 697)
      - Arts HR 12894 (Box 697)
      - Atomic Technology HR 622 (Box 697)
      - Audits HR 4316; HR 7324 (Box 697)
      - Aviation Anniversary H.Res.1147 (Box 697)
      - Bankruptcy HR 12589 (Box 697)
      - Benefits HR 3315 (Box 697)
      - Beta Sigma Phi H.J.Res.943 (Box 697)
      - Beverage Containers HR 3246 (Box 697)
      - Bicycle Trails HR 1991 (Box 697)
      - Bolling Amendment H.Res.988 (Box 697)
      - Bonds, Municipal HR 7517; HR 9077 (Box 697)
      - Bookkeeping-Private Business HR 9863 (Box 697)
      - Bribery HR 7539 (Box 697)
      - Budget HR 5317; HR 12729 HR 7936; H.Res. 56 (Box 697)
      - Bullets HR 3625 (Box 697)
      - Census HR 5182 (Box 697)
      - CIA H.Res.l06 (Box 697)
      - Child Care HR 161 HR 4352-4353 (Box 697)
      - Child Development HR 155 (Box 697)
      - Child & Family Service HR 2967 (Box 697)
      - Civil Rights HR 2355; HR 2323; HR 3603; HR 2386; HR 7754; HR 13902 HR 13928 (Box 697)
      - Civil Service HR 180 HR 7701 (Box 697)
      - Clean Air HR 5220; HR 14559 698 (Box 697)
      - Commerce HR 1618; HR 1900; HR 7530 (Box 697)
      - Communications HR 171 (Box 697)
      - Congressional Preservations HR 1273 (S.632) (Box 697)
      - Congressional Reform H.Res.322 HR 3259; H.Res.328; H.Res.318; H.Res. 332; H.Res. 326 (Box 698)
      - Conservation H.Con.Res. 213 HR 4342; HR 5483; HR 6345; HR 8045 (Box 698)
      - Constitution (Spanish) H.Con.Res. 48 H. Con.Res.49 (Box 698)
      - Consumer HR 6602; HR 10873-empty; HR 3601; HR 2078; HR 3763; HR 3322; HR 5994; HR 170 HR1001; HR 7839; HR 7575 (Box 698)
      - Contributions HR 6080 (Box 698)
      - Copyright HR 7750 (Box 698)
      - Crime HR 4355; HR 8640 (Box 698)
      - Death Penalty HR 4134 (Box 698)
      - Defense HR 4133 (Box 698)
      - Discrimination H.Con.Res. 173 HR 5452; HR 5991; H.Res.276 HR 4350; HR 4354; HR 154;HR 4471 (Box 698)
      - HR 9013 (Box 698)
      - Drugs H.Res.1351 HR 5359; HR 11996 (Box 698)
      - Ecology HR 12928 HR 13047 HR 13098 (Box 698)
      - Economy HR 1523; HR 2156; HR 2170; HR 2139 (Box 698)
      - Economic Opportunity HR 5937 (Box 698)
      - Economic Rights HR 7552 (Box 698)
      - Education HR 5234; HR 5646; HR 5702; HR 12638 HR 12616.HR 8395 (Box 698)
      - Elderly HR 175-176 HR 179 H.J.Res.970 HR 7385; HR 7378; HR 12978 HR 13062 (Box 698)
      - HR 14085 HR 14089 HR 14093 HR 14097 HR 14099 HR 14103 HR 14453 HR 14509 (Box 698)
      - Emergency Financial Assistance HR 7701 (Box 699)
      - Emergency Loans HR 7422; HR 7751 (Box 699)
      - Employees HR 3934; HR 4240; HR 6020; HR 5023; HR 7597; HR 5451 (Box 699)
      - Employment HR 50 HR 1609; HR 4481; HR 5851; HR 2209; HR 4446; HR 3924; HR 8028; HR 12357 (Box 699)
      - HR 13295 HR 13295 (Box 699)
      - Energy H.Res. 604 H.Con.Res.37 H.Res.658 HR 1573; HR 5211; HR 14696 HR 5928; HR 8494 (Box 699)
      - Environment HR 6159; HR 7997; HR 4658 (Box 699)
      - Equal Rights H.J.Res.208 HR 4347 (Box 699)
      - Exporters HR 7712 (Box 699)
      - Family Planning HR 164, HR 43 (Box 699)
      - Family Service HR 2966 (Box 699)
      - Federal Employees HR 5451 (Box 699)
      - Federal Service HR 13 (Box 699)
      - Federal-State Assist. HR 178 (Box 699)
      - Financial Assistance HR 3823; HR 13351 (Box 699)
      - Financial Disclosure HR 2684; HR 2359,3788 (Box 699)
      - Financial Incentives HR 7333 (Box 699)
      - Financing Campaigns HR 9100-9101 (Box 699)
      - Fire Island HR 6456; HR 3994 (Box 699)
      - Firearms HR 5132 (Box 699)
      - First & Fourth Amendment s HR 2566 (Box 699)
      - Fiscal Year H.J.Res.499 (Box 699)
      - Food & Drug HR 42 (Box 699)
      - Food Day H.J. Res. 877 (Box 699)
      - Food Production HR 6153; H.Res. 364; HR 12747 (Box 699)
      - Food Stamps HR 2412; HR 2567; HR 181 HR 1860; HR 2412; HR 2508; HR 2081; HR 8466 (Box 699)
      - Foreign Affairs H.Res.1304 (Box 699)
      - Foreign Assistance HR 6382 (Box 699)
      - Foreign Missions HR 12 (Box 699)
      - Funds H Res. 229 (Box 699)
      - Funds for BIA H.Res.233 (Box 699)
      - Funds for Forest Roads H.Res. 230 (Box 699)
      - Funds for National Parks H.Res.232 (Box 699)
      - Funds for Public Lands H. Res. 231 (Box 699)
      - Funds for Great River Road H.Res.234 (Box 699)
      - Gateway Nat'l.Rec. Area HR 1781 (Box 700)
      - Guns HR 7874; HR 3202; HR 5132 (Box 700)
      - Handicapped HR 2422 (Box 700)
      - Health H.Res.901 H.J.Res.956 HR 2304; HR 3674; HR 4155; HR 5519; HR 2954; HR 4340; HR 3485; HR 4925; HR 5719; HR 5518.HR 3957; HR 2570; HR 6283; HR 7364; HR 7375; HR 8489 (Box 700)
      - Health Insurance HR 7604 (Box 700)
      - Health Security HR 21 (Box 700)
      - Health Services HR 9474 (Box 700)
      - Historic Sites HR 163 (Box 700)
      - Holocaust Remembrance H.J.Res.894 (Box 700)
      - Housing HR 1567; HR 2504, 2980; HR 4485; HR 1566-1567 BSA Amendment Housing Act of 1937 (Box 700)
      - HR 11214 HR 13598 (Box 700)
      - Human Environment H.Res. 28 (Box 700)
      - Humanitarian Assist. HR 5715 (Box 700)
      - Hunger HR 2438 (Box 700)
      - Immigration HR 2565; HR 14392 S. 3094 (Box 700)
      - Income Tax HR 4191; HR 2204 (Box 700)
      - Indian Affairs HR2526 (Box 700)
      - Indochina HR 168 H Res. 129 H.Res.134 H.Con.Res.21 (Box 700)
      - Interns H.Res.159 (Box 700)
      - Internal Revenue HR 157 HR 621 HR 1570; HR 1624; HR 1659; HR 4358; HR 5299; HR 3010; HR 2166 (Box 701)
      - HR 4897; HR 4358; HR 5842; HR 5867; HR 5990; HR 6712; HR 4195; HR 4189; HR 4562; HR 3632 (Box 701)
      - HR 3302; HR 1624; HR 3447; HR 2066; HR 2734; HR 3065 (Box 701)
      - Internal Revenue HR 2981; HR 621 HR 8224; HR 8497; HR 12426.HR 13632 HR 13735 HR 13275 HR 14565 HR 4061 (Box 701)
      - Israel H.J.Res.528 (Box 701)
      - Jobs HR 4306; HR 3090; HR 12972 (Box 701)
      - Jordan--Missiles H.Con.REs.34 (Box 701)
      - King, Martin Luther HR 1811; HR 13849 H.Con.Res.97 (Box 701)
      - Kluczynski Building HR 4172 (Box 701)
      - Labels HR 4150; HR 42 (Box 701)
      - Labor HR 7348 (Box 701)
      - Land Use HR 3510 (Box 701)
      - Limousines HR 5882 (Box 701)
      - Lobbying HR 3045 (Box 701)
      - Long-term Care H.J.Res.474 (Box 701)
      - Mail HR 4294; HR 1623; HR 8049; HR 3582 (Box 701)
      - Marihuana HR 6108; HR 4520 (Box 701)
      - Mayaguez H.Res.536 (Box 701)
      - Medicaid S.3205 (Box 701)
      - Medical Relief HR 3897 (Box 701)
      - Medical Services HR 8152-empty (Box 701)
      - Medicare HR 7330 (Box 701)
      - Metric System HR 6030 (Box 701)
      - Military H.J.Res.29 HR 167 HR 7476; HR 5924; HR 7225 (Box 701)
      - Military Aid to Indochina H.Con.Res. 29 (Box 701)
      - Military Selective Service H.J.REs.29 (Box 701)
      - Mint Buildings HR 5620 (Box 701)
      - MIA HRes. 335 (Box 701)
      - Moroz, Valentyn H.J.Res.1019 (Box 701)
      - Mortgage Payments HR 5398 (Box 701)
      - Mortgage Disclosure HR 7446 (Box 701)
      - Mountain Names H.Res.1227 (Box 701)
      - Name Prefixes HR 160,4351 (Box 702)
      - National Autistic Child. Week H.J.Res.472 (Box 702)
      - National Food Day H.J .Res. 384 (Box 702)
      - Nat'l. Foundation on Arts & Humanities HR 12838 (Box 702)
      - Congress National Parks HR 6576 (Box 702)
      - National Seashore HR 7407 (Box 702)
      - National Wilderness S.1384 (Box 702)
      - News Media HR 172 (Box 702)
      - No-fault insurance HR 1272; HR 285 (Box 702)
      - Noise standards HR 14027 (Box 702)
      - Nuclear fuel HR 7553 (Box 702)
      - Nuclear materials HR 6082 (Box 702)
      - Nurse training S.66 (Box 702)
      - Nursing homes H.Res.306 HR 5547; HR 6055; HR 5233; HR 7339; HR 7291; HR 7282; HR 7321 (Box 702)
      - HR 7342; HR 8653 (Box 702)
      - Oil H.J.Res.366 S.701 HR 5289 (Box 702)
      - Older Americans Act HR 3922 (Box 702)
      - Olympics HR 13490 (Box 702)
      - Parole HR 5726; HR 2322 (Box 702)
      - Petroleum H.J.Res.386 (Box 702)
      - Planning HR 5728 (Box 702)
      - Pollution HR 14543 HR 4170-4171 (Box 702)
      - Postage HR 4313; HR 5400 (Box 702)
      - Postal service HR 9203; HR 56 (Box 702)
      - Poverty HR 5937 (Box 702)
      - Preservation HR 9187 (Box 702)
      - Price control HR 5150 (Box 702)
      - Prison Reform HR 2324 (Box 702)
      - Privacy HR 2635; HR 5438 Buckley HR 5128-5129; HR 2330; HR 2655; HR 169 HR 171-172 (Box 702)
      - HR 13681-1368 (Box 702)
      - Property Tax Relief HR 153 (Box 702)
      - Protective Services HR 12 HR 11184 (Box 702)
      - Public Health HR 7384; HR 7336; HR 7345; HR 7361; HR 7367; HR 7372; HR 7377; HR 8212 (Box 702)
      - Public Hearings HR 11007 (Box 702)
      - Public Meetings HR 10315 (Box 702)
      - Public Service Act HR 12547 (Box 702)
      - Public Works HR 6683; HR 5247; HR 12970 (Box 702)
      - Railroads H.Con.Res. 574 (Box 703)
      - Rape HR 162,4355-6 HR 12685 (Box 703)
      - Recycling HR 6011 (Box 703)
      - Refugees HR 13640 (Box 703)
      - Rehabilitation HR 543 (Box 703)
      - Resources- Energy HR 5048 (Box 703)
      - Responsibilities of the House.HRes.140 (Box 703)
      - Retirement--Federal HR 1639 (Box 703)
      - Salaries--Justices HR 13881 (Box 703)
      - School lunch HR 4222 (Box 703)
      - Secret service HR 12760 (Box 703)
      - Secretary of State HR 9201 (Box 703)
      - Securities HR 8765 (Box 703)
      - Select Committee on Intelligence HRes.1100 (Box 703)
      - Senior Citizens HR 3922 (Box 703)
      - Sewall-Belmont.HR 163 (Box 703)
      - Sex HR 5452 (Box 703)
      - Sex discrimination H.Res.73 H.Res.30 HR 160 HR 166 H.Res.276 HR 4477; HR 4482; HR 4354 (Box 703)
      - HR 9013 (Box 703)
      - Small Business HR 13784 (Box 703)
      - Social Security H.J.Res.402 S.1559 HR 906 HR 1939; HR 2902; HR 4772,4774 H.Con.Res.10 (Box 703)
      - HR 3764; HR 4357; HR 156 HR 159 HR 165 HR 1669; HR 1804; HR 159,4359 HR 6055; HR 3009 (Box 703)
      - HR 4747; HR 5564; HR 6283; HR 7431; HR 7388; HR 7381; HR 7273; HR 7285; HR 7318; HR 7300 (Box 703)
      - HR 7315; HR 4315; HR 4357; HR 8467; HR 5376; HR 5374; HR 4341; HR 5957; HR 156 HR 177-178 HR 1804; HR 180 HR 9652; HR 10284 HR 8461; HR 6699; HR 5743; HR 7032; HR 9280; HR 7303; HR 7267; HR 7270 (Box 703)
      - Social Security HR 7276; HR 7279; HR 7288; HR 7309; HR 7306; HR 7327; HR 7429; HR 7772 (Box 704)
      - HR 1970; HR 7996-7998 HR 8343; HR 8467-8468 HR 8516-8518 HR 8635; HR 9188; HR 9652-9653 (Box 704)
      - HR 10284 HR 12269 HR 14264 H.Res.1168 HR 12836 HR 11840 HR 12837 HR 13062 HR 13482 HR 14107 HR 14263 HR 14105 HR 14101 HR 14091 HR 14149 Related material-2 foldes (Box 704)
      - Solar Heating HR 4507 (Box 704)
      - Solid Waste Disposal HR 8745 (Box 704)
      - South Americans H.Con.Res.67 (Box 704)
      - South Vietnam HR 5715 (Box 704)
      - Soviet Jews H.Con.Res. 55[?] (Box 704)
      - State Requirements HR 7294 (Box 704)
      - Suits against D.C. HR 10304 (Box 704)
      - Sunshine Bill HR 11656 (Box 704)
      - SST H.Res.l022 HR 10287 HR 4933 (Box 704)
      - SSI HR 165 (Box 704)
      - Supplementary Income HR 7261 (Box 704)
      - Tariffs HR 57,10824 (Box 704)
      - HR 3906; HR 13581 HR 14590 (Box 704)
      - Taxes HR 715 HR 251 HR 240 HR 2224; HR 2422; HR 3733; HR 5217; HR 12349 HR 6360; HR 13803 HR 12992 H.Con.Res.42: HR 7714; HR 7053; HR 6629; HR 3216; HR 8369; HR 1809; HR 6353 (Box 704)
      - HR 10219 HR 7546; HR 7587; HR 10245 (Box 704)
      - Trade HR 6066; HR 5585; HR 3960; HR 9172; HR 5358 (Box 705)
      - Unemployment HR 6900; HR 4464; HR 17597 HR 13330 HR 2398; HR 4462 (Box 705)
      - Uniform Services HR 164 (Box 705)
      - Unit Prices HR 4551 (Box 705)
      - United Nations HR 1845 (cont.) H.Res.677 (Box 705)
      - U.S. Code HR 14055 HR 10922 (Box 705)
      - Veterans HR 13022 HR 174 HR 3311; HR 3423; HR 5305; HR 5312; HR 5895; HR 7355; HR 8406 (Box 705)
      - HR 9144; HR 9146; HR 9148; HR 13600 HR 13675 HR 14283 (Box 705)
      - Vietnam H.Con.Res.24 (Box 705)
      - Visas HR 173 (Box 705)
      - War Material HR 4679 (Box 705)
      - War, Nuclear HR 7223 (Box 705)
      - War Powers HR 12255 (Box 705)
      - Waste Disposal S.2l50 (Box 705)
      - Water Pollution S. 396 HR 7637 (Box 705)
      - Wilderness HR 7819 (Box 705)
      - Wildlife Preservation H.J.Res.388 (Box 705)
      - Wills, Frank H.Con.Res. 13[?] (Box 705)
      - Women PL 93-380; H.J.Res.287; H.Res. 371; HR 1565; H.J.Res.212; HR 4346; HR 4350; H.Con.Res.3C (Box 705)
      - Women--IWY HR 9924; H.Con.Res.76[?] (Box 705)
      - Women's Equality Day H.J.Res.969 H.J.Res.996 H. J .Res. 30, 286-287 (Box 705)
      - World Peace Tax Fund HR 4897 (Box 705)
    - Resolutions: (Box 706)
      - HR--Introduced (Box 706)
      - HR--Co-Sponsored (Box 706)
      - H.Con.Res. Introduced (Box 706)
      - H.Con.Res. Co-Sponsored (Box 706)
      - H.Con.Res., H.J.R. Nos.11-135l--62 Folders (Box 706)
      - HR 1--200 (Box 707)
      - HR 201-1700 (Box 707)
      - HR 1701--5500 (introduced) (Box 707)
      - HR 1701--5500 (co-sponsored) (Box 707)
      - HR 5501-11007 (introduced) (Box 708)
      - HR 5501-10802 (co-sponsored) (Box 708)
      - HR 7001--7800 (Box 708)
      - HR 7801-11000 (Box 708)
      - HR 11007—15424 (Box 709)
      - HR 11001-13599 (co-sponsored) (Box 709)
      - HR 13600--20000 (co-sponsored) (Box 709)
    - Copies of bills filed numerically in individual Folders: (Box 710)
      - HR 12--543 (Box 710)
      - HR 621--2398 (Box 711)
      - HR 2414--4925 (Box 712)
      - HR 5023--7388 (Box 713)
      - HR 7404--9924 (Box 714)
      - HR 10054--12978 (Box 715)
      - HR 13022--15134 (Box 716)
  - Subseries V.3: Legislation--General
    - 87th-- 92nd Congresses (Box 717)
    - 93rd Congress Public Laws (Box 718)
    - 93rd Congress: (Box 719)
    - Reports (Box 719)
    - Senate Bills and Resolutions (Box 719)
    - 93rd Congress HR 1-9442 (Box 720)
    - 93rd Congress HR 10036-17597 (Box 721)
    - 94th Congress: (Box 722)
    - Public Laws (Box 722)
    - Senate Bills (Box 722)
    - 94th Congress: (Box 723)
    - House Bills--miscellaneous (Box 723)
    - Reports (Box 723)
    - Resolutions (Box 723)
    - Bills to be Reintroduced (Box 723)
    - Legislation--Related items (Box 723)
  - Subseries VI.4: Legislation--Voting Record
    - 92nd Congress: (Box 724)
      - Member's Personal Voting Record: Bella S. Abzug (1 volume) (Box 724)
      - Democratic Study Group: Record Votes, (3 volumes) (Box 724)
      - League of Women Voters Political Accountability Rating (1 Folder) (Box 724)
    - 93rd Congress: (Box 725)
      - Member's Personal Voting Record: Bella S. Abzug (1 volume) (Box 725)
      - Democratic Study Group: Record Votes, (2 volumes) (Box 725)
      - Congressional Quarterly: Roll Call 1973 (1 volume) (Box 725)
    - 94th Congress: (Box 726)
      - Member's Personal Voting Record: Bella S. Abzug (1 volume) (Box 726)
      - Democratic Study Group: Record Votes, (2 volumes) (Box 726)
      - Voting Record--miscellaneous (1 Folder) (Box 726)
  - Subseries VI.5: Legislative Accomplishments
    - [undated] (Box 727)
    - 1971-1976 (Box 727)
    - 92nd Congress (Box 727)
    - 93rd Congress, (3 Folders) (Box 728)
    - 94th Congress (Box 728)
    - 93rd & 94th Congresses; miscellaneous (1981 Addition) (Box 728A)
- Series VII: Public Statements
  - Subseries VII.1: Press Releases
    Primarily mimeograph copies, a few with notes and related items. These are in individual Folders; the headings, not listed, include date and catch-word title of each release.) See also: Restrict Files, 1981 Addn.
    - 1 December 1970--29 -June 1971 (Box 729)
    - 2 July 1971--27 -November 1971 (Box 730)
    - 1 December 1971-15 -February 1972 (Box 731)
    - 16 February 1972--29 -March 1972 (Box 732)
    - 1 April 1972--30 -September, 1972 (Box 733)
    - October 1972--28 -February 1973 (Box 734)
    - 1 March 1973--30 -June 1973 (Box 735)
    - 2 July 1973--30 -October 1973 (Box 736)
    - 1 November 1973--30 -April 1974 (Box 737)
    - 1 May 1974--27 -February 1975 (Box 738)
    - 3 March 1975--30 -May 1975 (Box 739)
    - 5 June 1975--31 -October 1975 (Box 740)
    - 5 November 1975--10 -February 1976 (Box 741)
    - 12 February 1976--31 -May 1976 (Box 742)
    - June 1976--29 -November 1976 (Box 743)
    - Washington Office Files:
      - 1972; 1973; 1974 (Box 744)
      - 6 January 1975--27 June 1975 (Box 745)
      - July 1975--31 October 1975 (Box 746)
      - 5 November 1975--31 December 1975 (Box 747)
      - 3 January 1976--31 March 1976 (Box 748)
      - 1 April 1976--30 June 1976 (Box 749)
      - 2 July 1976--14 December 1976 (Box 750)
  - Series VII.2: Congressional Record Statements (Reprints and Clippings)
    - January 1971-15 July 1971 (Box 751)
    - 16 July 1971-15 November 1971 (Box 752)
    - 16 November 1971-16 December 1971 (Box 753)
    - Clippings and mimeographs, January-December (Box 753)
    - 1972 (Box 754)
    - 1973 (Box 755)
    - 1974 (Box 756)
    - 1975 (Box 757)
    - 1976 (Box 758)
    - Subject Index, 92nd--94th Congresses (Box 758)
  - Subseries VII.3: Newsletters
    - Congresswoman Bella S. Abzug Reports, 1971-1976 (Box 759)
    - Be!la Abzug in Congress, 1975 (Box 759)
    - (For newsletter of National Constituents of Bella Abzug, see Box 65; for newsletters of others and correspondence relating to newsletters, see Box 66) (Box 759)
  - Subseries VII.4: Speeches and Remarks
    - n.d., miscellaneous (Box 759)
    - [1971] HUB Conference, Chicago (Box 759)
    - 1971
      - 3 February Senate of Youth, D.C. (Box 759)
      - 1 & 3 February Floor Remarks (Box 759)
      - 7 April FBI Investigation (Box 759)
      - 23 April Home Economists, Rochester (Box 759)
      - 30 April Report to the Lower East Side (Box 759)
      - June Special Order on Indochina (Box 759)
      - 1 June New York City Statehood (Box 759)
      - 7 June To Citizens Interested in Child Care (Box 759)
      - 18 June Interstate Association of Commissions on the Status of Women, St. Louis, Mo. (Box 759)
      - Breakthrough to Political Equality (Box 759)
      - 29 June To Delete the Space Shuttle (Box 759)
      - 10 July National Women's Political Caucus (Box 759)
      - 12 July N.W.P.C. (with Chisholm statement) (Box 759)
      - 21 July Labor-H.E.W. Bill (Facilities for Retarded) (Box 759)
      - 21 July National Press Club--Women in Politics (Box 759)
      - 6 October Equal Rights Amendment (Box 759)
      - 20 October Resolution of Inquiry (Box 759)
      - 2 November Amchitka (Box 759)
      - 9 November Floor Remarks--A Plot Against the Children (Box 759)
    - 1972
      - 18 January Resolution to Censure Nixon (Box 759)
      - 2 February Chisholm's Presidential Candidacy (Box 759)
      - 12 February W.E.D.S. Conference, Nashville (Box 759)
      - 29 March Amnesty (Box 759)
      - 10 April Civil Rights of Homosexuals (Box 759)
    - 1976
      - 17 May Senate Candidacy (Box 759)
  - Subseries VII.5: Speeches and Remarks, 1970-1974 (1981 Add.)
    - Women's Strike for Peace December 1970 (Box 759A)
    - Women's Rally, Bryant Park 26 August 1970 (Box 759A)
    - Central Coordinating Committee, Women's Strike for Peace 5 December 1970 (Box 759A)
    - Lettuce Workers Rally 15 January 1970 (Box 759A)
    - Women in Political Life 1970 (Box 759A)
    - Acceptance Speech, Election Night November 1970 (Box 759A)
    - Jewish Center of Kew Gardens 18 December 1970 (Box 759A)
    - The Case for Abandoning the Seniority System December 1970 (Box 759A)
    - My Plans for Congress December 1970 (Box 759A)
    - Fairleigh Dickinson 7 January 1971 (Box 759A)
    - West Side Chamber of Commerce 13 January 1971 (Box 759A)
    - Martin Luther King Meeting 14 January 1971 (Box 759A)